[theme music playing]
[Julio] We Ardientes offer
our condolences, Miss Aguas.
[Ivy] Take me away.
I want to get out of this town.
Arnaldo, is this yours?
Yeah, that's mine.
I've been looking for that.
-Where are you going?
-I'm going to look for Arthur.
I'll convince him
to continue being a witness.
[Arthur] After everything
I've been through
at the hands of the Ardientes,
I don't want to come out of hiding.
I'd rather they think I'm dead.
[Raul] Have dinner with me.
Let's fix everything as husband and wife.
[Natalie] This is the beginning
of your downfall, Emilia.
[Diego] I won't put you in danger.
I'll make sure we have enough evidence
before you testify in court.
[Arthur sobbing]
[Ivy] Mr. Mayor, I want you to choose
which one of these
I should use to kill you.
[Emilia] I don't want my son
to end up with that bitch.
[Diego] I'll follow Ivy and Arnaldo.
I need to protect Ivy
because I don't trust Arnaldo.
[police officer] She's determined
to catch and punish
whoever murdered Carlotta.
He should be careful.
Miss Aguas might be planning
something against him.
[Arnaldo] Why are you playing hard to get?
[Ivy] Just don't give up.
I promise you that the efforts you've made
and the time you've spent waiting
will be worth it.
Promise.
[somber music playing]
[tense music playing]
Hello, Aunt Camia?
Ivy and Arnaldo are currently
at the Ardientes' resort.
I'm on my way there.
[Camia] Be careful, Diego.
Thank you for watching over my daughter.
Don't mention it.
Anything for Ivy.
Take care.
[tense music playing]
[engine revving]
[engine powers down]
[smoke hissing]
Mister!
-Sir?
-Is there an auto shop nearby?
-My car broke down.
-It's a bit far from here.
Just walk down the road,
and you'll see a small shop.
-Okay, thank you.
-No problem, sir.
[Julio] According to our insider…
Ivy suspects there's foul play
involved in Carlotta's death.
She never told me that.
[Julio] That's why you better
watch your back.
I have a feeling she's suspicious of you.
She could be planning something.
Now, I'll get to her first.
I'll send my men over to abduct Ivy…
and bring her to my happy place.
Whatever her plan is…
I'll squeeze it out of her brain.
That woman is going to regret
the day she was born…
and she'll wish she was dead
before I get through with her.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Arnaldo?
Arnaldo, are you still there?
Uh, yes, Grandpa. Just a second.
[Julio] Hello?
-Is that your grandpa?
-[whispering] Yes.
-Work?
[Ivy] Ah, work…
We had a deal, remember?
No work. Just…
play all day, right?
Fine, then.
I'll just find someone else to play with.
I'll just finish this.
Hello, Grandpa?
Hey.
Just wait for our men, okay?
I'm telling you…
That woman will regret she lived
once I'm done making her suffer.
There's no need for that.
What?
I won't let you hurt Ivy because
she's not doing anything wrong.
[Julio] What?!
How sure are you?
I think she's starting to like me.
Everything is falling into place,
and it's only a matter of time
before we become a couple.
[scoffs]
I trust her, Grandpa.
She'd never betray me.
I have to go.
[unsettling music playing]
Are you done?
Can you rub some lotion on me?
Sure.
Here.
[moans]
Okay, enough.
Let's eat first.
I have to finish that later.
We'll see.
Okay, let's eat!
[upbeat music playing]
Hi!
-Can you help me?
-Yeah, sure.
[Ivy chuckles]
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
Oh! Oysters.
All right.
[Prianka] Casanova, the greatest lover…
loved eating oysters for breakfast.
It was his favorite aphrodisiac.
[tense music playing]
Want one?
Of course.
Cheers.
[tense music playing]
Yum.
-It's cold.
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
Here.
-Here.
-Oh, thank you.
I need to dry my legs.
[sighs]
Sorry.
I'll get us some drinks.
No. Stay here.
Do it later.
Arnaldo, stop.
Things are happening so fast.
Sometimes, I think
you're just leading me on.
[sighs]
Why would I do that?
You're playing push-and-pull on me.
One minute you're hot,
the next thing you're cold.
What do you really want?
Tell me the truth.
I already told you that
I'm not like your other girls.
I have self-respect.
Don't you understand that?
[sighs]
[sighs] Okay.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Arnaldo…
I do want to give myself to you.
But only at the right time and place.
If you wait…
I'm sure…
you'll get a huge reward from me.
All right.
I'll wait.
Good boy.
-Okay, I'll get our drinks.
-No.
No, just…
stay here.
I'll get it.
Just wait for me here.
Behave.
Wait for me.
[exhales]
I'll do it.
Just get me another bottle of wine.
Okay, ma'am.
[ice clinks]
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
Arnaldo.
It's enough.
-Cheers.
[glasses clink]
You know what? You're right.
I'm used to dating easy women.
Think about it, just like Natalie.
After our first date, she was all over me.
But what happened?
It's over. I got tired of her.
But, with you…
You're different.
Arnaldo…
I'm not just doing this for you.
This is who I am.
I know, and it's driving me crazy.
[unsettling music playing]
Arnaldo, have you been obsessed
with a woman before?
What kind of question is that?
Well…
We're here now, so…
I want to know you more.
Okay. Well, to answer your question,
what's the craziest thing I did
for a woman I loved?
Maybe, it was when I beat up
my rival in college.
That's it?
For an Ardiente like you…
I'm disappointed.
Why? What did you expect me to say?
Murder.
People say that…
the Ardientes are murderers.
So, I just want to know…
if you…
Have you…
Arnaldo…
Have you killed someone…
in the name of love?
[screaming]
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
I wouldn't do that.
I was raised differently.
Grandpa taught me to use
my brain over my emotions.
If you let emotions take over…
you could end up killing someone.
And I can't let those things happen.
Sure. I believe you.
-Cheers?
-Cheers.
Is it good?
It's perfect.
You don't look satisfied.
Do you want more?
You.
I want you.
[melodramatic music playing]
[tense music playing]
[thump]
[tense music intensifies]
[tense music fades]
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
[tense music fades]
[tense music playing]
Your death isn't enough payment
for what you did.
I won't let you off that easily, Arnaldo.
I won't taint my hands
with blood for someone like you.
You deserve a fate far worse than this.
[tense music intensifies]
[melodramatic music playing]
Mark my words…
You'll meet the same fate
as Nanny Carlotta.
I'll make you suffer so much
you'll want to kill yourself.
It won't be revenge.
It'll be justice.
[tense music playing]
Wait, Raul.
Hold on.
This isn't right.
Something's off.
[scoffs]
What do you mean this isn't right?
I'm your husband. You're my wife.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I don't know if…
this is serious or
just another game of yours.
-I don't want to get hurt again.
-Shh…
Emilia, what do I have to do…
for you to trust me
and believe that I love you?
I'll do it.
Just tell me.
Kneel before me.
Kiss my feet.
Do you want me to ask
for your forgiveness?
No.
Worship me.
[unsettling music playing]
Raul, no…
Emilia…
I love you so much.
I would worship you.
[melodramatic music playing]
[engine starts]
-Is it okay?
-Yes. Turn it off.
[engine powers down]
It's fixed. I changed the fan belt. See?
Thank you.
Here's the payment.
-Thank you.
-Mister…
-Is La Union far from here?
-It's about an hour away.
-All right, thank you.
-You're welcome.
[engine revving]
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Hi.
I thought you'd never wake up.
-What time is it?
-Almost noon.
I see. What happened last night?
A lot.
Well, you drank a lot.
You were really drunk.
[sighs] I almost left,
but I felt sorry for you.
Ouch!
Why am I wounded?
Because you were too rowdy.
You accidentally cut yourself
with a knife.
Did…
Did something happen
between us last night?
What?
Did something happen
between us last night?
You know…
If something does happen,
I'll make sure you remember it.
You won't ever forget it.
So, nothing happened.
Maybe next time.
Come on.
Breakfast is ready.
I'll just see you downstairs.
Okay.
Good morning.
[unsettling music playing]
Mom, I'll be fine.
I'm just worried that Arnaldo
will do something to you.
If you're worried about Arnaldo…
I can take care of myself.
I'm more worried about you.
Are you going to see the farmers today?
Yes, dear.
The farmers' cooperative
invited me to give a talk.
Mom, don't go anywhere
without your bodyguards.
You need to be careful,
especially now that I'm out of town.
Yes, dear.
Be careful, Mom.
I will, dear. Don't worry about me.
Bye.
Hi!
-Good morning.
-Let's eat.
Thanks.
What do you want?
-Maybe some coffee?
-No, this is perfect.
You're perfect.
Arnaldo…
-Let's eat.
-Yeah.
[sighs]
Good morning!
Hi, sexy.
Wow!
That looks delicious.
Who's more delicious? The food or me?
[chuckles] Do you have to ask that?
Of course…
It's you.
You're more delicious than the food.
[chortles]
Good answer.
-Raul?
-Yeah?
Can you please slap me?
I want to make sure I'm not dreaming
because I still can't believe
we're finally getting along.
No, Emilia.
You're not dreaming.
Come here.
From now on, you have to get used to this.
Things can only get better.
[sighs]
I love you.
[tense music playing]
Sir Diego! It's been a while
since you came here.
-Is Arnaldo here?
-Yes, sir.
He's with his guest at the rest house.
Okay. Don't tell him I'm here.
I want to surprise him.
Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
-Okay, sir.
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Auntie?
-Diego.
I've got some bad news.
What happened?
A typhoon hit the area.
The co-op office was hit pretty bad.
The winds were so strong that
they destroyed the roof and walls.
We were able to save
some campaign materials,
but most of them got ruined.
I'll have it fixed when I return.
[Loring] That's good to hear.
But do we have funds?
Don't worry about it. I'll find a way.
That's great.
You're a true leader indeed.
You don't give up that easily.
[Pandoy] Go, Diego! Go!
-Right, everyone?
-Go, Diego!
Diego will help us--
-[metal crashing]
-[screaming]
-My goodness!
-What's happening there?
-Watch out!
-Be careful!
It's just one of the metal roof sheets.
The wind blew another one away.
I promise I'll have it fixed
when I return.
Thanks, Diego.
Take care of yourself, all right?
Take care!
I will. Be safe too.
[water drizzling]
[tense music playing]
Diego?
I almost killed you.
Why are you here?
To watch over you.
I don't trust Arnaldo.
You'll ruin my plans.
-Leave now.
-No.
I'll stay here to protect you.
[knocking on door]
Ivy?
Ivy, are you there?
-[whispering] See?
-[knocking on door]
Ivy.
[knocking on door]
Uh… Arnaldo, yeah! Wait a second!
[whispering] You have to hide!
Ivy? [knocking on door]
[knocking continues]
Ivy, open the door.
I'm coming!
[knocking on door] Ivy.
[knocking continues]
-Yes, Arnaldo?
-Ivy!
I'm coming! Hi!
What took you so long?
-Is there a problem?
-Um…
Arnaldo…
Come here.
[Ivy moans]
I was just changing,
that's why I took so long.
Okay. Well, I came here because
I want you to come with me.
-Where?
-Just come.
I'll bring you to a special place.
Okay? Let's go.
All right.
Hang on.
[tense music playing]
Um…
Yeah.
-Can we still use those?
-Yes, they're fine.
[Loring] We need to prepare
for the meeting.
-We need to saw this off.
-Oh, dear!
-Let's cut this, okay?
-Miss Camia is here!
-It's Miss Camia!
-Here she is!
Everyone, it's Miss Camia!
-Ma'am!
-Miss Camia.
-Oh, no!
-Ma'am.
Miss Loring, what happened here?
It got destroyed by the typhoon.
But it won't take long
for us to fix it, ma'am.
-Please have a seat.
-Don't worry about me.
Is there anything I can do to help?
-No, it's fine.
-Don't worry about us.
-We got this. Have a seat.
-Thank you, Nimfa.
Ma'am, this won't take long.
-We'll fix it so we can start.
-Don't worry about me.
-Hurry up, everyone!
-I got this, Miss Loring!
-Are you okay, ma'am?
-I'm fine, thanks.
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
I can wait. Don't worry about me.
-Pandoy.
-What?
Aren't you supposed to dry that up?
I'm on it.
Perfect!
I like it.
[chortles]
Ew!
Why?
Is that Emilia's?
-[chuckles]
-She smells old!
[puffs and whines]
I think you should take a shower.
You know what, Natalie?
Right now, I'm in control
of the situation.
That's why I can provide you
with everything you need.
But you have to give me what I need too
so I can tell you everything
you want to know.
Well…
What do you need?
Money?
Guns?
Hmm…
An army?
All of the above.
I need to be stronger than the Ardientes.
[Camia] The Ardientes aren't
the ones keeping us
from getting the justice we deserve.
They are not our biggest enemies, either.
It is fear.
Fear stops us from fighting for justice
that the Ardientes have long withheld.
So, we must rise above our fears!
-That's right!
-Yes!
They cannot oppress us if we are united!
Miss Camia is right.
-Long live the new Ardiente!
-[farmers] Long live!
-Long live!
-Long live the new Ardiente!
-[all] Long live!
-[applause]
-[melodramatic music playing]
When I was a kid,
I'd always come to this place to be alone.
When Grandpa would look for me,
he'd know to find me here.
It's a special place,
and I want to share it
with a special someone,
and that's you.
Arnaldo…
Arnaldo, behave!
How long will you keep me waiting, huh?
I'm sorry.
I promised my parents that
I'd only give myself
to the person I love most.
To my future husband.
You mean to say all this time,
you were a virgin?
Yes.
Yes, Arnaldo.
[unsettling music playing]
[tense music playing]
Wait.
-[Arnaldo grunts]
-What happened?
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine. I just tripped.
-Look, I brought you this.
-Oh! Thank you, Arnaldo!
I'm okay. It's just a scratch.
We should go back to the rest house.
-Come on.
-Okay.
[Arnaldo sighs]
Okay, let's go.
-Are you sure you're okay?
-I'm okay. Really.
-You sure?
-Yes.
-Do you like it?
-Yeah.
-[Arnaldo grunting]
-We're almost there.
-Okay, sit down.
-Wait, I can do this.
[grunts]
Okay. Oh, wait.
I have painkillers in the car.
Stay here. I'll get it.
-Just wait here, okay?
-Okay.
Diego.
[romantic music playing]
Ivy, I just want to make sure
that you're safe.
I understand that.
But let me reiterate that
I won't do anything that'll get me killed.
I can protect myself.
If you need me, you know where to find me.
Thanks. You should go. Take care.
Ivy, be careful.
[unsettling music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
Oh, dear! Here we go again.
We haven't even recovered yet,
but here comes another storm!
-Give Dolfo some of that too.
-Thank you.
-Miss Camia, have some juice.
-Thank you, Nimfa.
That was a very beautiful speech.
You're my idol! You're so inspiring.
Thanks for all your help.
[sighs]
The truth is…
my family is suffering
under the Ardientes too.
That's why I'm doing this.
Do you have any available jobs for me?
I can work for free as a volunteer.
Well…
Nimfa, your help with
Diego's campaign is enough.
[thunder rumbling]
Mm…
This is delicious.
Thank you. I made it myself.
You know, this is my daughter's favorite.
Her name is Lily.
Really?
Where is she?
[somber music playing]
She's gone.
Oh.
Is she dead?
[somber music playing]
Miss Camia…
Don't worry.
Even if your daughter is gone…
we'll always be here.
We support you.
-Let's eat more fritters.
-Okay.
[both chuckling]
-It's so delicious.
-Thank you.
Congressman.
Who's that from?
It's from a certain Jaguar.
They want to enter the
gambling scene here in Ardiente.
You brought me this
without even checking it?!
What if it's a bomb, and it kills us all?
Jaguar?
I've never heard that name before.
Probably a newcomer.
A newcomer?
Why don't they come here and face me?
Congressman, I asked them about that too,
but they said it's not the right time.
What an arrogant.
Open it. Find out what it is.
[unsettling music playing]
Take that away and burn it.
As you wish, Congressman.
This newcomer has some nerve.
Kittens aren't welcome in my business.
Only wild animals can mingle
with the Ardientes.
[unsettling music playing]
Jaguar.
The congressman did not accept your gifts.
Get ready. We have a mission.
[mahjong tiles shuffling]
[poker chips rattling]
[man] Who are you?
What do you want?
Is this a joke?
-Who's your stupid mascot?
-[laughing]
[grunts]
[gunshots]
[screams]
Tell your boss…
that we own this gambling den now.
What?!
Do you know who my boss is?
Congressman Julio Ardiente.
He owns this gambling den,
so if you've got a brain,
you wouldn't go against him.
[gunshot]
Who wants to be next?
Tell the congressman…
that the Jaguar is here…
and he will rule Poblacion Ardiente.
[ominous music playing]
Arnaldo, I couldn't find your painkillers.
[sighs]
It's here.
That's good. How's your leg?
Actually, I feel a lot better.
Especially now that everything
is finally clear to me.
What do you mean?
I saw Diego.
So…
What is he doing here?
-I don't know.
-Enough!
Enough.
-You're toying with me.
-Of course not! No!
What's going on between you two?
Nothing, Arnaldo.
Nothing.
Grandpa was right.
Mom was right.
-Arnaldo, listen to me.
-No.
I'm done playing your games.
I'm done.
[unsettling music playing]
-Arnaldo! Arnaldo, wait!
-What?
-What?!
-Listen to me.
Give me one good reason
why I need to stay!
Hmm?
Please, give me one good reason
to trust you.
[unsettling music playing]
Arnaldo…
I love you.
Stay.
Stay, Arnaldo.
I love you.
[unsettling music playing]
-For the Jaguar.
-Jaguar!
[Julio] I have had many encounters
and many threats
in my political career.
But I'm telling you,
this group is different.
This group is dangerous.
[gunshots]
[Diego] You're going to marry the man
who might've killed Nanny Carlotta?
I'll do everything I can to stop
your wedding with Arnaldo.
[theme music playing]